(Sheldon:)I don't understand.
(Leonard:)She's enjoying living with you
(Leonard:)and she didn't want it
to end early.
(Sheldon:)So, she's deceiving me
(Sheldon:)in order to spend
more time with me.
(Raj(singing):)Yes.
Oh.
(Sheldon:)Well, I feel both
flattered and hurt.
(Sheldon:)Like when people say I
look like that skeleton
from Nightmare Before Christmas.
(Raj:)Oh my God, that's
who you look like.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, this is not a big deal.
(Leonard:)It's a little white lie,
everyone does it.
(Raj:)Not me,
I'm a 100% honest
(Raj:)in all of my
relationships.
(Howard:)And how single
are you right now?
Eating-cake-on-the-toilet
single.
(Sheldon:)Well, I won't tolerate
deception in my relationship.
(Sheldon:)I have no choice
but to confront her.
(Howard:)Don't do that,
you've got gold here.
(Howard:)Hang onto it until
you're in trouble
(Sheldon:)and then...
throw it in her face.
(Penny:)What?
(Leonard:)Why would you tell him that?
(Leonard:)That's terrible advice.